Arthur Fernandes M Santos (S) +34 644 350 581







I recently graduated in Software Analysis and Development from Unicesumar (Brazil), able to create reponsive web pages from the scratch, creating designs, making layouts and programming. I have experience working with data manipulation, data analysis and customer support, working in big teams and multicultural environment. As a journalism graduated, I learned how to comunicate, understand people and their complexity and how to get messages passed by without losing its meaning.

Work Experience

DATA IMPLEMENTATION SPECIALIST - DOCTORALIA ESPAÑA

BARCELONA, SPAIN. MAY, 2021 - CURRENT

Management and manipulation of big databases to generate specific formats, necessaries to new clients implementations. Process organization and maintenance to guarantee data protection and information quality in company system. Contacting with all involved teams, keeping the process flowing to ensure that every step works as the company standards, and training new import members.

arthurfms@yahoo.com

DATA ANALYST - DOCTORALIA BRASIL

CURITIBA, BRAZIL. MARCH, 2021 - MAY, 2021

Improve data analysis for Marketing, lead generation and DP phone operations, update and maintenance workflows to optimize data collection. Generate dashboards and data insights for all related teams, focusing on new leads, keep and improve operation control, goals update and team commission standard.

SUPPORT ANALYST - DOCTORALIA BRASIL

CURITIBA, BRAZIL, SEPTEMBER, 2019 - MARCH, 2021

Provide support for employees and users with doubts, bugs corrections with scripts on SaaS, Marketplace and financial system. Report weakness, find solutions to prevent bugs, and notify developers about necessary corrections by Jiras. Data report creation and analysis based on Support and Customer Success actions and needs.

Helped to stablish a data implementation process improving support side actions, reducing +16 hours of work and ensuring scalability to the service.

LATAM CUSTOMER SUCCESS ANALYST - DOCTORALIA BRASIL

CURITIBA, BRAZIL, APRIL, 2019 - SEPTEMBER, 2019

Assist health professionals from Chile by phone and email. Made usability training and helping them with platform issues, setting the environment for new clients and keeping track of their needs. Follow client's engagement and guarantee the best usage from the system, generating best results and helping them to achieve their goals.

TRILINGUAL CALL CENTER AGENT - SYKES BRASIL

CURITIBA, BRAZIL. SEPTEMBER, 2018 - APRIL, 2019

Manage corporate cards request in English, Portuguese and Spanish. Credit card limit raises requests, account information and client needs. Receive and follow client's request, managing their information following all companies process.

Skills

HTML	
CSS	
JS	
SQL	
GIT	
EXCEL	

Education

SYSTEMS ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT

UNICESUMAR. JAN, 2021 - AUG, 2022

2,5 years tech graduation, passing through the main issues and skills for a developer, including system requisits, programming languages, UI and many others topics.

JOURNALISM

UNIVERSIDADE METODISTA DE SÃO PAULO. JAN, 2013 - DEC, 2017

4 years bachelor graduation on Journalism and social comunication, where I won the best tesis prize from the graduation year with a photojournalism book about ancient culture on Argentina's northeast.

Language

Portuguese - Native English - Advanced Spanish - Advanced

Other Courses

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

PRACTICUM BY YANDEX. FEB, 2022 - JAN, 2023

HTML CSS JavaScript
GIT React BEM Methodology

FRONTEND ENGINEERING

EBAC.

JAN, 2022 - JAN, 2023

HTML CSS Sass Bootstrap

JavaScript Ajax React JQuery